mark.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy · Mark

We at MARK.COM ("Mark"), pride ourselves on providing you, the customer, with a range of online products and services. As part of this process, we ask you to provide us with certain personal information, for example, your name, address, email address, and payment details.

## Protecting your privacy

Mark takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our customers and ensure that the personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without the customer's consent.

However, there may be times when Mark may be required to disclose personal information of a customer without their express consent. This may occur where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the customer or another person who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of Mark or its associates, licensors, affiliates, other customers or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; or required by law.

## Why we need to obtain personal information about you

Your personal information is used to enable us to deliver our online products and services to you. Our products and services require registration and requirement includes certain personal information about you so we can generate revenue and issue a payment to you. Some Mark licensors require that we share certain account details about you in order for us to monetize your traffic, but not your payment details.

## What we do with your personal information

It is important for you to maintain your account details current and accurate at all times, to ensure continued service and commission earnings. Your email address and other personal information may be used to enable us to send you marketing or promotional material (such as promotional offers) on other products and services that we consider may be of interest to you.

You may, at anytime, change, delete and modify your account profile by logging into your account and edit your personal information. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

The information you provide to Mark may also be shared among some of our licensors, subsidiaries and the operators of our affiliated websites.

## How we collect information about you

Directly from you, such as when you enter your personal details on our websites to register or subscribe to our services); Indirectly, by keeping a record of our users IP addresses and through the use of "cookies".

### Use of IP addresses

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to review aggregate information, and to audit the use of our site. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

### Use of cookies

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll find them at most major Web sites.

By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the mark.com service will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized settings.

You may also get cookies from our sponsors or advertisers websites. Mark, has no control over this.

### Use of web bugs

What are web bugs? A web bug is an electronic tag that is placed on a web page. It can be used to count the number of visitors to our sites and gather information and develop profiles about people who visit our site and/or click on links on our sites. Such devices are also known as 'invisible' or '1-by-1' GIFs due to their incredibly small size which usually cannot be detected. 

We use web bugs on our websites to track both the source and destination of visitors to our sites. This is required for proper accounting and reporting requirements of our affiliate program as well as to help us to provide our visitors with what they want to see and do online.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to the terms and conditions contained herein (as amended from time to time). If you do not agree to be bound by its terms, we politely ask that you do not use this site.

If you have any question or concerns about Mark’s Privacy Policy please Contact Us.
